Anany Srivastava: Mapping
Saatvik Rawat: Mapping
Harsh Kumar: Mapping
Mohit Kumar Singh: Mapping
Harshit Shukla: Mapping
Rajat Mangat: Mapping
Chaman Kumar: Mapping
Surbhi Saxena: Mapping
Supriya Verma: Mapping
Akanshu Rana: Mapping
Jatin Gupta: Mapping
Abhishek Yadav: Mapping
Himanshu: Mapping
Rifa Fatima: Mapping
Mayank Arya: Mapping
Deepak Gupta: Mapping
Anany Srivastava: Direct
Garvit: Mapping
Arpit Rajput: Mapping
Raghvendra Pratap Singh: Mapping
Abhinav Kannaujia: Mapping
Dhaval Jain: Mapping
Anany Srivastava: Assiciative
Ayushi Goel: Mapping
Anany Srivastava: Set associative
Soni Kumari: Mapping
Harsh Kumar: Direct
Set Associate
Garvit: Direct mapping associative mapping
Surbhi Saxena: Direct and associative
Dhaval Jain: Direct
Chaman Kumar: Set associative
Rishabh Shakya: Direct
Supriya Verma: Direct set associative
Jatin Gupta: Direct
Associative
Set associative
Dhaval Jain: Associative
Shruti Jain: Mapping-Direct, association and set associative
Akanshu Rana: Direct
Associative
Set- Associative
Himanshu: Direct,associative,set-associative
Rajat Mangat: Direct, associative, set associative
Shruti Jain: Replacement
Harsh Kumar: Replacement
Akanshu Rana: Replacement
Rifa Fatima: Replacement
Soni Kumari: Replacement
Garvit: Replacement
Anisha Singh: Replacement
Himanshu: Replacement
Manik Upadhyay: Replacement
Jatin Gupta: Replacement
Supriya Verma: Replacement
Dhaval Jain: Replacement
Mohit Kumar Singh: Replacement
Ayush Mohan: Replacement
Rajat Mangat: Replacement
Ishitwa Agrawal: Replacement
Surbhi Saxena: Replacement
Raghvendra Pratap Singh: replacement
Himanshu Chaurasiya: relpacement
Anany Srivastava: Replacement
Rishabh Shakya: Replacement
Rydam Agrawal: Replacement
Abishek: Replacement
Vipin Paswan: Repcement
Ayushi Goel: Replacement
Pulkit Goyal: Replacment
Abhinav Kannaujia: Replacement
Akhilesh Verma: replacement ?? Non Dirty , DIRTY
Ayushi Goel: Dirty
Dhaval Jain: Dirty
Akhilesh Verma: ND, D which will be copied in main MM
Anany Srivastava: D
Harsh Kumar: Dirty
Supriya Verma: Dirty
Raghvendra Pratap Singh: D
Saatvik Rawat: Dirty
Jatin Gupta: Dirty
Rajat Mangat: Dirty
Dhaval Jain: Dirty
Devesh Kumar: Dirty
Mohit Kumar Singh: D
Akanshu Rana: D
Rydam Agrawal: Dirty
Rifa Fatima: Dirty
Chirag Agrawal: DIRTY
Ishitwa Agrawal: d
Garvit: D
Soni Kumari: Dirty
Abhinav Kannaujia: Dirty
Harshit Shukla: Dirty
Pravisht Goel: Dirty
Abishek: D
Surbhi Saxena: Dirty
Deepak Gupta: Dirty
Shristi Shukla: Dirty
Shruti Jain: Dirty
Harshita Singhal: Dirty
Vipin Paswan: D
Manik Upadhyay: D
Devansh Kumar: D
Akhilesh Verma: 12+67
Garvit: 79
Dhaval Jain: 79
Pulkit Goyal: 79
Himanshu Chaurasiya: 79
Akanshu Rana: 79
Mayank Arya: 79
Rishabh Shakya: 79
Saatvik Rawat: 79
Rifa Fatima: 79
Jatin Gupta: 79
Rydam Agrawal: 79
Harsh Kumar: 79
Supriya Verma: 79
Harshita Singhal: 79
Devesh Kumar: 79
Vipin Paswan: 79
Rajat Mangat: 79
Deepak Gupta: 79
Harshit Shukla: 79
Danish Siddiqui: 79
Himanshu: 79
Anisha Singh: 79
Shivani Singh: 79
Pravisht Goel: 79
Raghvendra Pratap Singh: 79
Ayush Mohan: 79
Surbhi Saxena: 79
Abishek: 79
Jigyansh Varshney: 79
Rohit Tomar: 79
Shruti Jain: 79
Eklavya Singh: 79
Abhinav Kannaujia: 79
Arpit Rajput: 79
Anany Srivastava: 79
Ishitwa Agrawal: 79
Shubhang Verma: 79
Pulkit Agarwal: 79
Soni Kumari: 79
Abhishek Yadav: 79
Vikas Kumar Singh: 79
Devansh Kumar: 79
Aditi Maheshwari: 79
Shivanshu Srivastava: 79
Ayushi Goel: 79
Himanshu Chaurasiya: 79
Pravisht Goel: Change in aligment of North and South pole
Shruti Jain: By changing alignment of North South
Rajat Mangat: N-S=0
S-N=1
Chirag Agrawal: Change in aligment of North and South pole
Chirag Agrawal: 79
Ayushi Goel: Change in alignment
Darpan Varshney: Change in aligment of North and South pole
Darpan Varshney: 7o
Darpan Varshney: 79
Akhilesh Verma: 45-98
Pulkit Goyal: -53
Devansh Kumar: -53
Saatvik Rawat: -53
Darpan Varshney: -53
Ujjwal Singh: -53
Preetika Jain: -53
Ayushi Goel: -53
Chirag Agrawal: -53
Mayank Arya: -53
Devesh Kumar: -53
Chaman Kumar: -53
Vipin Paswan: -53
Jatin Gupta: -53
Rajat Mangat: -53
Deepak Gupta: -53
Pulkit Agarwal: -53
Rifa Fatima: -53
Shivani Singh: -53
Raghvendra Pratap Singh: -53
Abhishek Yadav: -53
Harsh Kumar: -53
Supriya Verma: -53
Garvit: -53
Harshita Singhal: -53
Anisha Singh: -53
Rishabh Shakya: -53
Ayush Mohan: -53
Sparsh Mittal: -53
Abhinav Kannaujia: -53
Pravisht Goel: -53
Himanshu: -53
Shruti Jain: -53
Eklavya Singh: -53
Shikha Gupta: -53
Surbhi Saxena: -53
Abhinav Kannaujia: -53
Abishek: -53
Danish Siddiqui: -53
Harshit Shukla: -53
Shristi Shukla: -53
Soni Kumari: -53
Rydam Agrawal: -53
Rashmee Pandey: -53
Arpit Rajput: -53
Dhaval Jain: -53
Shubhang Verma: -53
Harsh Harit: -53
Anany Srivastava: -53
Rohit Tomar: -53
Ishitwa Agrawal: -53
Akanshu Rana: -53
Himanshu Chaurasiya: -53
Aditi Maheshwari: -53